Question 1:
Use for loop, while loop and recursion to write down a function which can sum of given numbers.

Question 2:
Write down a function which staggered merge elements in arrays.
For example, given [a，B，C] and [1，2，3], function return [a，1，B，2，C，3].

Question 3:
Write down a function which prints top hundred of Fibonacci number.
By definition, the first two numbers in the Fibonacci sequence are 0 and 1, each subsequent number is the sum of the previous two.
For example, top ten of Fibonacci number is: 0,1,1,2,3,5,8,13,21,34.

Question 4:
Write down a function which arrange all natural number into biggest number.
For example, given [50，2，1,9], function return 95021 which is biggest number.

Question 5:
Write down a program which given 1,2,...9 (cannot change order), return always 100 use operator + , - , or nothing.
For example, 1 + 2 + 34 – 5 + 67 – 8 + 9 = 100.

Translate: iigmir